Let's do some training before
going to Akhisar, shall we?
You will fight against both
of us alone, father, right?
That might be a
bit difficult for you.
It is not the number of men
that brings victory in battle.
It is the courage that
brings victory in war, sons.
Make your move.
Are Alps ready for the conquest?
We are always ready, my
Bey. We are strong and brave.
You are fast.
But not enough for me.
-Alaeddin.
-My Bey.
Tell me, how are you
going to attack the castle?
We will hit from the left wing, my Bey.
And also from the right wing, my Bey.
We will attack from all fronts and
bring Akhisar down just like this, my Bey.
What if another unit comes from behind?
What will you do then?
Brother, behind you
We always have a watchman behind us, my Bey.
Don't worry.
Father... Don't father.
Don't hurt my brothers..
You three think you are
equal to us if you gather, huh?
It's not that easy.
-Don't..
Don't, father, don't hurt them.
Look at me.
You are cheating.
You know my weak spot well.
They should pray for you. You.
Bala.
Come here.
My family could have been by my side too.
My mother, father, maybe my siblings.
You took them all from me.
Meryem.
What are you doing here? -I...
...saw you coming to the cemetery
alone, so I didn't want to leave you alone.
Besides, I am considered
one of the Sisters now, right?
Yes. Right.
Who is it?
She is my little girl who will never grow up.
Children are like embroidery, Meryem daughter.
Even if they are gone,
their mark always remains.
A family is the same.
The pain of their absence is big.
But this pain keeps me standing.
The loss of a child or..
..the loss of a mother..
...hurts people from the same place.
But anger and hatred...
...burn your heart.
They leave you in the dark, Meryem daughter.
I won't find peace without
taking revenge on those infidels...
...who took my
family, Bala Hatun.
This revenge keeps me alive.
-If you allow me.
-Meryem.
I really like you, Meryem.
You remind me of my youth.
I'm glad you met Fatma.
I'm glad you came to our tribe.
God has shown His justice.
You took my mother...
...and He took your daughter.
I long for you in such a
way that my daughter....
...I look for you in every new face I see.
I will make you pay for
all the suffering I endured.
My Bey.
The council is ready, they are waiting for you.
Orhan, Alaeddin. You go on.
Come on, my daughter.
Meryem.
Bring some sherbet, my daughter.
Sure, Bala Hatun.
Drink some sherbet before
going to the council, my Bey.
So you care for your husband, huh?
You are my only one, Kara
Osman. Who else would I care for?
So you are the Meryem..
...Fatma talks about all the time.
It's an honor to meet you, Osman Bey.
Let me help you.
I am sorry.
I got excited.
It's okay. Take this.
So, tell me.
Are you from nearby tribes?
Do we know your family? Your father?
We are nomads.
We just arrived here.
They killed my mother and
father when I was little, Osman Bey.
Meryem will join the Sisters, my Bey.
She is being trained.
So, you will become a Sister, huh?
You are brave.
The courage of your heart shines in your eyes.
I will do everything I can to take
revenge for my family, Osman Bey.
The path of the Sisters and
ours is not the path of revenge.
Our path is the path of justice.
The scales of justice must be set with patience.
Otherwise, we will become oppressors.
Yes, Osman Bey.
Go now.
Thank you my daughter, thank you.
Bala, I am going to see the Beys.
The man who took my family and my childhood.
But how can I be so weak
when I am close to them?
God, let me be strong.
Alps! Someone's coming
Stop!
You are on the border of Kayi. Who are you?
I am the envoy of the glorious
Mongol State's Head Commander...
...who makes everyone kneel...
...and who brings an order to the world...
...Ulugan.
What are you doing here?
We are here to demand
your Osman Bey's allegiance...
...and collect the tribute we imposed on him.
If you stand in our way, your
fate will be the same as these fools.
If you don't want to be dragged
behind my horse, step aside.
We won't let you cross our border
with the corpses you drag behind you.
We will inform Osman Bey!
I will go there however I want.
-Neither you nor Osman can stop this.
-Alps!
Attack!
The fate of those who stand
against the Mongols is death.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
We are going to Osman's tribe. Come on!
Blood! Blood! Blood!
Saruca Bey.
Your father Bayhan Bey...
...sacrificed his life for his state
and nation without hesitating.
Now his property and his cause are yours now.
Beylic of Kizilcinarogullari will be ruled...
...by you, Saruca Bey.
May Allah keep you on the right path.
Aameen, my Bey.
The right path is your path, my Bey.
May Allah give you a long life.
Thank you, thank you.
I appreciate it.
Beys, Karesi Bey...
...who supported heathens
all the time with your help
as well and valued his
interest above anything else...
...has lost his reputation and
also the chance to stop us.
Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
From now on, we will discuss
our new target and what to do.
At dawn, we will reach Akhisar
and start hitting the walls.
Okay, my Bey.
My Bey.
Akhisar is a nest of heathens with solid walls.
Can we destroy them by shooting with catapults?
Begum Hatun, you mus be thinking...
...alps will fall weak and impatient...
..if the siege of Akhisar takes
longer than expected, right?
Remember this.
Our hearts burning to
bring justice in those lands...
...are stronger than their walls
inside which they hide their oppression.
Lukas and Sofia will see that too.
Listen to me carefully now.
Cerkutay. Boran.
You two will be in the front line with me.
Orhan and Alaaddin.
You will be in the left wing.
Begum Hatun.
And Saruca.
You two will be in the right wing.
-As you order, my Bey.
-I want no mistakes.
We'll never fall into despair.
Until the call of Muhammad
is recited in the square...
...of Akhisar and the flag
of Kayi raises on the walls,
...we'll never stop.
God willing
Hurry up, hurry up.
-Faster.
-Go over there.
Commander Lukas.
A message from our scouts.
Osman completed his preparations secretly.
Come here, Osman.
Come.
There should be no holes in the walls!
Repair them all.
Take the long-ranged bows up on the walls.
Take the Greek fire with you.
I'm forbidding you to use sleep...
...and even rest till this battle ends!
Is that clear?
-Yes, commander!
-Hristo, guide them.
Soldiers, come on
Karesi turned out to be an old coward, huh?
He couldn't stand against
Osman but just ran away.
We will stand, Sofia.
We won't give Osman even a single fortress.
Any news from Lord of Iznik?
Are the reinforcements coming?
Don't worry.
When Osman attacks our walls
...we'll hit him from
somewhere he never expects.
In the back.
He thinks he can beat me,
my Shahzade(Prince).
What now? What?
What is this? Are you ripping Ghazi in two?
We haven't eaten all
together for long. Right, Ghazi?
Right. You never stop fighting, my Bey.
You take my father with you as well.
Are you complaining, Ghazi Alp?
No, Boran Bey.
But everybody goes to the fight
and I stay with hatuns in the tribe.
You should be strong enough
to carry steel swords first.
Your father is right, Ghazi.
-There is still time for that.
-The matter between you and me is settled.
Don't mess with me anymore,
tall Shahzade(Prince).
-Right, Gonca Hatun?
-Yes.
Ghazi Alp is right.
Don't mess with him,
Tall Shahzade(Prince).
Alright then. Let's eat all together.
Let's eat.
Meryem.
Join the table, girl. Eat.
I don't want to disturb, my Bey.
You won't be disturbing anyone.
Take a seat, girl.
Everybody in the tribe
has a place in this table.
If you don't take me to the
fight, I will go myself, father.
Behave.
Sister.
Do Ghazi's words remind you something?
-Ha? Ha, my Bey?
-Yes, yes.
But it wasn't a good incident.
-Right, Fatma?
-Father...
Don't.
Don't tell, please.
Tell, Alaaddin.
Alright, my Bey.
Ghazi.
At your age
...Fatma insisted on fighting.
Then...
One day, our sister was...
What sister?
Come here, Halime.
Oh, I know her!
-No!
So... did she go?
Of course she did
She hid in the cart.
And fell into the battlefield all of a sudden
And when she came back
You won't believe this!
She kept saying "I should
have never gone there, my Bey!"
"It was too early for me." Right, Fatma?
Father.
How could you tell Ghazi about this?
He'll talk about it for days.
I should tell him, of course.
Actually, you know what she did?
She also attempted to take
her deceased sister with her
..but her mother didn't let.
Oh Fatma... You gave us a rough time.
I will bring some halvah(a type of dessert).
You know what, my Bey? Holofira
should say a table prayer for us.
Well...
Mother, your son is making fun of
me as I can't say the words correctly.
-Orhan...
-Mother... My Bey, I was...
It was just a joke... I'm sorry.
Well...
Meryem, how is your training with Sisters going
Thankfully, Fatma
Hatun takes care of me.
But I'm a slow learner.
Don't mind what she says, father.
She holds the sword strongly.
And she's a quick learner.
The trainings will make you stronger.
Your patience too. And..
And they will restrain your anger.
Here we go.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate. You may start.
Enjoy the meals.
Thanks to Allah
...my father is combing my hair again.
I feel scared whenever you go on a duty.
-Thinking you may not come back.
-No, I don't believe that.
My pretty daughter...
My little gazelle is afraid of nothing at all.
I'm a little wolf, though.
A little wolf from the lineage of Kayis.
Look at this little wolf!
Father, when will we talk to Osman Bey?
When will we tell him we are Kayi as well.
Kayi?
Will we keep hiding the fact that
your grandfather is Sungur Tegin?
My pretty girl.
We already talked about this.
Never talk about this before I
mention this subject, alright?
Can I come in?
You can, Begum Hatun.
I couldn't find any time
to thank you earlier, Ilbay.
I still remember that I got out of
Karesi's dungeon thanks to you.
Don't even mention it.
Osman Bey gave me a duty and I carried it out.
Fine.
Still, I owe you one.
Thank you.
My father saves everyone.
When I get older,
I will be like him.
I can see that.
You are brave like your father.
You will be a tough woman.
I want to give you this mirror as a gift.
Through it, you can see how
much you take after your father.
Thanks, Begum Hatun. This is beautiful.
Thank you, Begum Hatun.
Thank you.
I haven't seen her so happy for long.
But why did you?
I didn't help you hoping something in return.
I didn't give her that in return for the favor.
It's been Ayse Hatun and me.
Well... I should go now.
Good night.
Begum Hatun.
Gonca.
Welcome.
I wanted to thank you
but I couldn't find a chance.
No need for that.
I have to. You protected me and my secret.
I owe you one.
You're wrong, Begum Hatun.
I protect neither you nor your secret.
If I had exposed the secret,
...there would have been no peace here.
If you didn't lead the troop of Kecilishah,
...I'd have told others by now.
Please, Gonca. I have no bad intentions.
I just fell in love.
And it was long before Bala.
-You don't understand...
-Hatun!
Do you have no shame at all?
The man who you said
you fell in with has a wife!
It was long before, I said. Long before.
There is no past or future for this matter.
From now on
...you will stay away from father and mother.
One mistake.
If you make one mistake, Begum
..I will expose the secret.
And you will be a total disgrace then.
-Gonca.
-I said my final words, Begum.
You either stay here with manners...
...or nobody will want to ever
remember your name when you go!
I helped you a lot...
...and you show ingratitude in return!
What was that?
Sister.
What does Gonca Hatun mean?
Where are you going?
Today, I've learned such a thing today...
...that nobody can send us away.
Well... Saruca will join Osman Bey's council.
He's got closer to Osman Bey. What will I do?
Then... Then you should hurry up.
Either you will be Osman Bey's son-in-law...
Or I will..
You will what?
I will find a way to rule Kayis.
Maybe save your life
during this conquest, Ilbay.
So I will pay back.
Don't mention it.
You owe nothing, Begum Hatun.
And I say I will pay.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
What's the news? Are the catapults on the way?
-Yes, my Bey?
Saruca and Yusuf are leading them. They
must be about to reach the headquarters.
Lukas and Sofia...
...will be trapped in Akhisar like rats today.
Today, Akhisar will the property of Kayis.
Our target is Akhisar!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Let's go.
Commander Lukas.
Preparations are almost finished.
We'll resist against Osman and his army.
Any news from the troop coming from Iznik?
They'll arrive in tomorrow morning.
I will welcome them, Lukas.
I know Osman's weakest spot.
I will lead the army.
When you attack from behind,
I will leave the fortress and hit!
I will make them face such a defeat...
...this field will be painted with their blood.
Osman will never be able to
take this fortress. Don't worry.
I have to go now.
Where? It's too soon.
I promised my little bird
Poena that I would meet her.
You never know, Lukas.
We may beat Osman without fighting.
Osman, where are you? Come out!
Who are you?
What's happening?
I am the envoy of Ulugan,
commander of the glorious...
..Mongol State.
The Bey of your tribe, Osman,
must step forward immediately.
Stop there, envoy. Calm down.
Osman Bey is not here.
Say what you have to say when
he comes. Now leave the tribe.
Otherwise, it will not end well.
Then, I will wait in your Bey's tent.
You must get through me first.
What's happening here?
Mother...
Mongols have no mercy.
Why have they come now?
We will now find out what they want, daughter.
Turhan.
What is happening here?
This man is a Mongol envoy, Bala Hatun.
Let him come close.
Since he is an envoy, he
must have something to tell us.
Listen to the Hatun and live a
long life. Otherwise, I will crush you.
Turhan.
Let him.
You did not come with
manners, but speak what you
have to say properly, and
then leave our tribe, envoy.
My Beys.
My Alps.
My lions who do not hold back from hardship...
...who rush into battle and
martyrdom without hesitation.
The time has come.
Today is the day of riot. Here is Akhisar.
And here we are.
I swear by the faith burning
in our hearts like a fire!
We swear!
By the swords that cast
fear into all infidels....
...with their gleam and
enlighten many minds, I swear!
We swear!
Today, we will be martyrs here.
But we will never stop until we
make Akhisar the homeland of Turks.
Allah is the Greatest!
Osman..
You..
...and those with you, those
shouting loudly, all of you...
I will make you cry out in
pain in the square of Akhisar.
My soldiers!
My fearless soldiers!
I know you are not scared of anything!
But I see fear in some of your eyes.
And I must say this to them, do not be deceived
by the Turks' loud noise, their best talent!
Do you hear them?
Do you understand what the Turks are saying?
They claim their God is greater
than ours, greater than Jesus Christ...
...greater than Holy Rome.
But they do not know
that we are the children
of a civilization that
has stood for centuries.
We are the descendants of brave
knights and ruthless legionaries.
Even if we knew we would drown
in our own blood, we would still fight.
We never run away from fighting.
Glorious soldiers of the
Great Empire, now I ask you...
These shepherds who invade your land
threaten your lives, and your religion...
Are you afraid of them?
No!
Are you afraid?
Then, until there is not
one left alive on this earth...
Death to the Turks!
I am listening to you.
Tell me.
We want...
...Kayis to kneel and pledge allegiance like...
...Germiyan, Candar...
...and all other Anatolian Beylics.
Or else..
..what?
It will be a shame, Hatun.
For all of you, for all your people,
and for your babies in the cradles.
Either you pledge allegiance, pay the
assigned tax, or you will be destroyed.
Look, envoy.
The Bey of our state, Osman Bey, is at war.
These are matters of state. When he returns...
..you will tell him.
He will come.
He will come and kiss our hands and feet.
Don't worry.
We say the envoy can not be blamed...
...but if you go any further, something
really bad is going to happen to you.
Hatun! -Stop there!
Know your place.
I hope your Bey does not pledge allegiance.
Then I will swim in your blood.
Nokers!
We will go and find Osman! Come on!
Mother...
What will we do now?
They will attack like mad dogs.
We will find a way out my daughter.
Stand tall.
Don't let the enemy sense your fear.
Turhan.
Let's make sure they left. Come on.
As you say, Bala Hatun.
We will keep attacking from all sides.
The infidels won't be able to
take a step beyond the walls.
We will not stop until we make a breach.
Right wing.
Left wing. Are the catapults ready?
The left wing is ready, my Bey.
The right wing is also ready, my Bey.
Our soldiers around the castle have
taken their positions as well, my Bey.
Okay.
Everyone to their duties.
-May our battle be blessed.
-Aameen!
While the catapults hit the walls,
you will watch all around the walls.
If you see a place where a breach
is about to open, you will inform us.
As you order my Bey.
Ayaz
Put the stones.
The time has come.
Today is the most blessed day for us.
Today is the day to take
revenge for the martyrs.
Today is the day to destroy
the enemies spreading poison.
O Allah
Come on, brother!
My Bey has started the attack, brother.
Come on Alps! Come on brothers!
Attack the infidels! Come on!
Allah is the Greatest!
-Saruca Bey. Come on.
-Come on.
Set.
Come on! Come on
This is for you Lukas!
In the name of Allah!
Osman.
Osman, the dust you raised from
Akhisar will not choke me, but you.
Hristo, take care of the wounded immediately.
Replace the dead ones right away!
Yes, commander.
Soldiers!
Look at our people.
They are really nervous and anxious.
Of course, they are.
They know how cruel the Mongols are.
What can they do? They are scared.
They are cruel.
They attack without caring
if they are young or old.
They attack treacherously.
That's why they come to our
tribe arrogantly asking for taxes.
I don't know the Mongols.
But I know one thing... Osman Bey
will never give them what they want.
We will never bow down, never!
Gather around me. Come on.
First, know this.
Your lives and property are entrusted to us.
May Allah bless you.
When Osman Bey successfully completes the
conquest, he will do what is necessary, God willing.
God willing.
Now the number of Alp
around the tribe will triple.
We will be cautious. We must be.
Everyone, back to your duties.
We will increase the precautions.
The Sisters must stay alert, my Fatma.
Make sure the new ones are well-trained.
Where is Meryem though?
You were going to take her for training...
She was here when the
Mongols came, mother, but...
Maybe she got scared.
We don't know her well but...
You are right. Just in case...
The Sisters will search around
and bring everyone they find, alright?
-Everyone, back to your duties.
-As you order, mother.
O Allah
Hit them
Hit those who took our Baysungur from us!
Hit those who martyred
Bayhan Bey and many others!
Hit, brothers!
The walls of this castle turned out to
be stronger than we thought, my Bey.
Boran!
I am sorry my Bey.
Even if it takes forever we will keep striking.
We will never give up.
Bring my horse.
-I will go and see myself.
-Okay my Bey.
You were right brother.
With these catapults...
...it is impossible to...
...damage these walls.
-Are the masters ready, Hristo?
-They are, commander.
There is a master at every wall.
As soon as there is the
slightest sign of hope for
the Turks, the masters
will repair it immediately.
-Come on. Come on brother!
-Allah is eternal!
Come on lions!
Come on brothers!
We will not lose our hope, come on!
My Allah, may You reward
our efforts. Come on, lions!
Allah is the Greatest!
They could only dust off the
walls with the catapults, sir.
These walls were built by the
greatest craftsmen of Bitynia, Hristo.
They are too strong to be
breached with attacks like this.
Osman will understand that.
He will lose his mind.
I will calm Osman's anger with my
own sword when the Nikea army arrives.
They covered the waterway.
Let's see where the entrance
to this water channel is.
Osman attacked Akhisar.
We are almost there. Commander Toygar.
From now on, Osman will not conquer
any place without our knowledge.
His moves will only be
determined by the Mongols.
He will either pledge
allegiance to us or disappear.
They say Osman never kneels before others.
Who is Osman not to kneel before us?
In our eyes, he is worth less than a mouse.
I want to see Osman.
Come on
Allah is the Greatest!
O Allah
We shoot the target every
time we make a move, for sure!
But brother... -But brother..
The stones we throw do not
even remove the dust of the walls...
...let alone open a breach.
But that breach will be opened eventually.
It will be, but the important thing is to...
...get in that castle before
our men get tired and hopeless.
Right. Right.
Brother..
We need to inform our father. Maybe...
..we can find another way, huh?
It doesn't seem like this will work.
I heard what happened.
Alps!
Gather!
Come here!
Listen well
What's the rule of conquest?
Patience comes from faith in our hearts!
We pray and embrace martyrdom!
For this reason
...I want no despair today!
My sons.
If someone falls
...you get him up.
You never stop until you
make holes in the walls!
You never stop shooting the walls.
Every stone you throw will
make the enemy tremble!
Our determination and tenacity...
...will scare the heathens.
For this reason
...they will be the ones to fall into despair.
When they come out of
those walls like rabid dogs
...they will taste our swords.
Ilbay.
I checked all the walls
my Bey. They are solid.
Yet in the north, there is a water
trough going under the walls.
You say so?
I missed you so much.
Why is Bala still alive? Is there a problem?
I have been waiting for a
message from you for days.
I'm avenging you, mother.
Lullaby, my dear baby.
Sleep well in your dream.
Aunt, I couldn't catch her alone.
-She was always with someone.
-Alright. Alright.
Alright, no problem.
You're among them now.
You can kill whenever you like.
I will kill.
I will kill them and help
my parents rest in peace.
You joined them.
You met them.
-What did you feel?
-Nothing.
I'm angry.
Like you said
...they try to seem good to everyone.
But I know the monster inside them, aunt.
Good, little bird.
Don't let their smiling faces deceive you.
Remember.
I got this prepared by Healer Martin.
For you to sleep well at nights.
Aunt, I couldn't sleep last
night because of nightmares.
What would I do without you?
Poena.
Are you awake?
My name is Halime.
-Poena.
-My name is Halime.
My name is Halime.
Poena.
-What's your name?
-Poena.
Poena...
Come.
Welcome, little bird.
Again.
-What's your name?
-Poena.
Poena.
Poena..
My hair looks beautiful, right?
Do you want your hair to be like mine?
You heard Poena.
Her hair will be like mine.
My little bird.
Come, come.
Well... What else is happening in their tribe?
Mongolians demand taxes from Osman.
Osman will never accept that.
They didn't respond as
Osman wasn't in the tribe.
They will visit their headquarters.
You've brought me great news, little bird.
Osman, you are in my hands now.
What will you do, aunt?
You'll see.
Now go.
Stay safe.
You're so precious to me.
Come on, come on.
You will never remember your filthy past.
You are my angel of vengeance.
Osman Bey Headquarters
We got a message from Samil patrolling in
the heathen lands beyond Akhisar, my Bey.
The army of Nikea, my Bey
...are marching towards
Akhisar with all their strength.
Lukas...
...gets support from Nikea, huh?
He does, my Bey.
They're going to reach Akhisar soon, my Bey.
While catapults keep shooting
the walls, we can divide
our army and confront
their reinforcements, but...
Of course we will confront them, but...
If we aren't careful
...Lukas may attack as we're outnumbered.
If we don't take action, we'll be an open
target between Lukas and the incoming army.
What's your plan, my Bey?
I will tell, Begum Hatun. I will tell.
We were planning to hit
the walls even for months...
But things have changed. Orhan, Begum Hatun.
You'll take your troops with Yusuf
and Ilbay and confront the army of Nikea.
As you order, my Bey.
But...
In case you fail to stop them,
...we will conquer the fortress by tomorrow.
The water trough Ilbay mentioned...
Boran, Cerkutay. My Bey. My Bey.
You two will get into there...
...and place the Greek fire
under the wall.
The spark we ignite will enlighten the dawn!
The enemy sleeping in
unawareness will be shocked
With Allah's will, Akhisar
will the property of Turks!
-God willing.
Boran Bey, Mongolians are approaching.
Mongolians?
Brother... What are they doing here, Cerkutay?
Alps, stand on alert.
Toygar.
Toygar?
Do you know that dog?
The butcher of Mongolians.
Brother.
It's not good that he's come here.
What are you doing here? Why did you come?
Cerkutay, born as a Mongolian with bad blood.
Don't be afraid. I'm not here for you.
I will teach Osman who his master is!
So...
Where is he?
Dogs like you never walk without their masters.
Cerkutay, you are a fiery boy.
You used to burn too fast like now. That's
why I like your brother more than you.
His brother?
Cerkutay.
Don't mention my brother's name...
...with your filthy mouth. Don't.
He said you made this
yourself and gave it to him.
He's deeply ashamed that
he's the brother of traitor like you.
He's dying to take revenge.
-Shut up!
-Cerkutay.
-Brother. Brother.
You are a dog whose leash
Osman is holding, Cerkutay.
I know you can't take this
dagger out of the sheath.
Cerkutay, brother! Brother!
Look... If you want to leave here
with your head on your shoulders,
...don't say another word.
Just tell me what you want.
You don't have a tiny piece of courage.
Inform Osman. I'm the messenger of Mongolians.
I will talk to him.
Wait here.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in, Boran.
My Bey, a Mongolian called Toygar...
Easy! Easy
Just wait.
Osman.
I see that you've forgotten
the power of Mongolians...
...and keep having raids.
I neither forget the past...
...nor stay away from
what awaits me in the future.
Your name is Toygar, huh?
Tell me now.
The one who sent you here as the
messenger... What does he demand?
Olcaytu Khan's mightiest commander...
...Ulugan has sent me.
You should know, Osman
...Ulugan never demands.
But he takes.
From you, we will take..
...loyalty oath to Mongolians and...
...ten carts of gold per year as the tax.
It's you who forgot the past.
Your commander..
Doesn't he know...
...Kayi never paid Mongolians a single coin...
...or pledged loyalty!
Ulugan isn't like other Mongolians, Osman.
He'll both take the gold...
...and make you kneel.
Ask...
...your dog Cerkutay.
He will tell you.
Look at me!
You're here as the messenger.
Don't push my patience.
Now go tell your commander...
...Osman doesn't accept any of your demands!
We didn't demand, Osman
...but just told you what we'll do next.
My Bey.
Those jackals set their eyes on us.
They'll attempt to jump on us soon.
You're right.
-Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
Go to the tribe quickly.
You never know what they can do.
Tell everyone to be more careful.
As you order, my Bey.
God willing, we'll get great news
about the conquest of Akhisar soon.
-God willing.
Until that time, we'll keep
tighter security around the tribe.
We placed watchmen inside and outside
the soup kitchen and the healing tent.
-Just in case.
-Good, girl.
Be careful. I want no mistakes.
You never know what vile
things Mongolians can do.
Yes, Cerkutay always tells me
about the cruelty of those nokers.
He still can't believe how he stayed among them.
-Is Cerkutay Bey a Mongolian?
-Yes.
I'm surprised.
-He was with those cruel Mongolians...
-You never know who can do what, Holofira.
You came from the castle of the lord.
Still no news from Meryem?
Do I have permission Bala Hatun?
Come in
Bala Hatun.
-Alps found Meryem. She was in Sogut.
-Let her in.
As you order, Bala Hatun.
What were you doing in Sogut, Meryem?
Why did you leave the
tribe without my knowledge?
Forgive me, Bala Hatun.
I felt scared as Mongolians came here.
Don't cry, girl.
Take this.
Now tell me everything.
Obviously, you were scared.
I wanted to see my grandmother.
I have nobody else, anyway.
I visited her grave and hugged.
I miss her so much.
I promise I won't go anywhere
without informing again.
This time, I ignore it because of
your age and inexperience, Meryem.
But...
...when you're scared come to us, right?
When you want to visit your
grandmother, you go to her with the Alps.
Thank you, Bala Hatun. May Allah bless you.
May Allah not let any of
His servants be all alone.
Meryem.
You are not alone.
Mother, if you allow me...
I want Meryem to be my helper.
Really?
I would really want that.
Of course I allow you, my daughter.
From now on...
Meryem will be your helper.
She will always be by your side.
I will fulfill my duty properly, Bala Hatun.
Who are you?
What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
Alps! Be the nightmare of those who are
dreaming of making Osman Bey bow down
Attack!
Nokers, attack!
May demons take your life, Osman!
I will punish you with my wrath!
You will not get away with this, Osman!
You will see the power of the Mongols!
Toygar will make Osman pay for this.
I spilled your dirty blood for this.
The Mongol blood on my sword will
become Osman's curse and will haunt him.
Come on
My Bey, Begum Hatun and Ilbay came.
My Bey.
Ayaz.
Where is my father Ayaz?
There was no one entering or
leaving since the guard shift, my Bey.
Nothing bad happened, God willing.
Aykurt.
My Shahzade(Prince)
Where is my Osman Bey, Aykurt?
I don't know my Shahzade(Prince).
Where would he go alone during a war?
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
May Allah bless you, my son.
I bothered you..
Why would this bother me, mother?
Don't say that.
My son.
Here, my son.
Do not bother, mother. Mother. Sit down.
-Son, is the soup good?
-It's good.
Thank you, son.
May no stones touch your feet.
May your hands never see hardship, mother.
May they never see hardship.
Tell me. Who are you?
I am a servant of Allah, striving
for the state on Allah's path.
Tell me mother.
Don't you have...
...a husband or a son to
take care of these for you?
My husband was martyred in
deceased Ertugrul Bey's army...
...and my son was martyred
in the path of our Osman Bey...
...the ruler of our state.
Only this orphan was left behind.
Once his hands hold a sword...
...I will also sacrifice him for the state.
Mother.
As long as mothers like you exist...
...this state..
..even if all of them come..
...even if all the enemies come...
...no one can make us kneel.
-Thank you.
May you and our children always be there.
Do you need food, son?
-Come and eat.
-I do, mother.
I am in need.
They call me Osman Bey.
Many soldiers stand behind me.
I am in need of your prayers.
My Osman Bey.
Open your hands. Mother.
Pray for me...
..and all my valiants..
...behind me.
Our wars..
...will reach victory through
the prayers of mothers like you.
Pray..
My son.
Come here.
Brother..
...what happened?
What are you thinking about while
we are here on duty, Cerkutay?
I buried...
...Mongol Cerkutay...
..and my past. But...
But..
...your past does not
let you go, right, brother?
We thought you had no one.
Why did you hide that you
had a brother for so long?
I'll tell you one day.
But what will change?
He sees me as his enemy.
Brother. Don't be upset.
He'll understand you in time.
We'll see.
But that's not the only problem, brother.
Hard days are waiting for us, Boran.
Those Mongols..
That man...
...never leave before he takes what he wants.
Brother..
When did the wolves let jackals hunt, brother?
We'll be the death of those who
disturb our peace, my Cerkutay.
For sure.
Then now...
...we will destroy these walls.
We'll bring honor to Akhisar,
the place ruled by dark spirits...
...with Islam.
God willing, brother, God willing.
Brother..
...the sun has begun to show itself, Cerkutay.
Come on.
Let's place the Greek fire around thoroughly.
Brother.
Put it in brother.
Come on brother.
That one. That one.
-Praise be!
-Alright.
You are done Osman!
You sealed your own death warrant!
You declared war not only on
me but on the Mongol state as well
Take this. Take this to Commander Ulugan.
When he receives the letter, he
will come here with all his armies.
Nokers!
Draw your swords!
For blood, for death..
...swing your swords!
Blood! Blood! Blood!
Tonight, we will shed blood
And so much blood will be shed that we will
witness the sunrise in a pool of blood.
We will burn and destroy
all the tribes that we find.
Osman will pay for what he did
Set out!
-Osman Bey Headquarters-
He is not around, my Shahzade(Prince).
We looked everywhere. There are
no tracks. And Iltutan is not in his place.
Orhan Bey.
What if something bad happened?
Do we need to send Alps,
my Shahzade(Prince)?
Attention! Osman Bey!
My Bey...
We were so worried when we could not find you.
We thought an important thing happened.
Conquests are not just for castles.
First of all, it is for the hearts.
Well, we shed a lot of blood and sweat for this.
But behind us are our people with prayers
in their hearts and tears in their eyes.
We should not forget them.
Okay, my Bey.
Send news to Bala.
She should establish a foundation immediately.
She should take care of everything personally.
We will solve all the problems of our people...
...with that foundation God willing.
As you order my Bey.
It is time to make our final move for Akhisar...
...which we've been surrounding for a long time.
Raid!
Kill them all! Show them
the furor of Erlik Khan!
Mother... Wake up
Wake up mother! Wake up
The dog whose time has come looks for its owner.
And you called for your owner, Osman.
You will be disciplined with blood.
Did you feel anything
wrong or strange while...
...placing the Greek fire
at the base of the walls?
No my Bey.
Those dogs didn't even notice.
They trust the walls they
hide behind so much, my Bey.
They seem to be in a deep sleep of unawareness.
It won't just be the cold frost that wakes
them from their sleep of unawareness.
When the breach is open... Saruca.
-My Bey...
You will get in with the army.
-Yes my Bey.
Come on lions.
Get ready.
Come on!
What is the latest situation, Hristo?
The catapult fire continued
until morning, Commander.
But only briefly during the night, and just
now, the attacks from the right wing stopped.
During the night and just now, right?
Commander, the Turks are
approaching from the right wing.
Did the walls take any damage?
-Why did they come here?
-The walls are strong, sir.
We just checked.
So, Osman is coming to his death, huh, Hristo?
Lukas!
Let's see if these walls
can protect you from me.
They are within our range. Archers!
The channel..
It's a trap!
Get off the walls immediately! It's a trap!
The real owners of the Holy Roman Empire
To protect what is yours, to stop the Turks,
you will fight to the last drop of your blood!
Come, Osman, come!
Come to your death
O Allah! Come on valiants!
Attack!
Damn it.
Where are you Sofia?
We will attack from behind with the
Nikea troops and divide Osman's units.
Lukas will attack with his armies...
...and make Osman suffer in hell.
Osman will die between
these two armies today, Sofia.
There's no way out.
They are approaching with the Nikea troops.
And that witch Sofia is leading them.
Good.
It's time for that head to be cut off.
Yes, Begum Hatun.
The jackal fighting with the wolf
throws up blood when the time comes.
Ilbay...
...now it's your turn.
Alps, we will stop them. Let's go.
Come now.
Your death is waiting for you here.
Now!
What is happening?
Where are they?
Bring the shields.
Come on, Begum Hatun. It's time.
Let's go, Alps! Allah is the Greatest!
Come on Alps! Come on valiants!
Before your sword sheds blood,
your head will be cut off, you witch.
Begum, so I start the slaughter with you, huh?
Someone's coming. Who are they?
It's Samil. Samil is coming.
Come on Ilbay! Come on
Show no mercy to the infidels.
Today, the fire of the infidels will be
extinguished. Allah is the Greatest!
-Praise be!
-My Shahzade(Prince).
-Thanks, Samil.
-I'd sacrifice my life for our Bey and Kayis.
Thank you, thank you.
Swing your sword then.
-Come on.
-Alright.
Alps!
The gate of conquest is here!
Attack the nest of heathens!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
-Open the gate! Come on!
-Alaaddin.
-Something's wrong, mother.
-We'll see.
Alaaddin. Alaaddin.
-Osman, Orhan.. Are they alright?
-Everybody is fine, thanks to Allah.
We besieged the fortress, but...
...Mongolians are back in the frontiers.
Their impertinent messenger
appeared before my father.
He came to the tribe
earlier. I just sent him away.
And we're keeping tighter
security. The tribe is safe.
Well done, mother.
You never know what
those rabid cannibals can do.
-We should be careful.
-Yes.
Bala Hatun
-My Shahzade(Prince).
-Turahan?
-Turahan, what's the matter?
-My Shahzade(Prince), bad news.
Mongolians raided the villages of Turks.
-What?
-They burned them down.
Vile dogs
You will wish you had never
destroyed this wall, Osman.
You will wish you had never met me.
Waiting for support from Nikea?
It's over!
You're on your own.
I'll send you to hell where you came from.
You can't bite me off.
You're going to die, Turk.
There is no tribe but death and
no ending but eternity, commander.
Now we will see who dies and who survives.
You'll never find peace in this land.
Come here, come.
Come to me. Come.
We'll never find peace in this land, huh?
It doesn't matter even if the
cruel loom over us like a storm!
We'll beat despair with our faith
and be victorious, for sure!
We'll break your evil and
make hope prevail in this land.
But you will never see that.
Dog.
-Attack, warriors!
-Stick your swords into dark chests of heathens!
Don't let them pass!
The jackal rising against
the wolf will be devastated!
And the world will flourish with
the glorious weapons of Kayis!
Damn it!
You won't be able to enjoy your
victory due to Mongolians, Osman.
Sofia is running off!
We will kill her one day.
Let's go.
Alps, keep your eyes wide open around the tribe!
Turahan, hold all the ways coming to the tribe.
Alps should carry the Greek fire just in case.
As you order, my Shahzade(Prince).
Come on, alps.
-Mother.
-Son.
Take care of the tribe, mother.
I will go fast and inform my father.
Be careful, Alaaddin. Don't worry, mother.
-Gonca.
-Alaaddin.
-Have a safe journey, my Bey.
-Thanks, hatun.
May Allah protect you.
Here we go.
Let's go!
Stay safe
Come on, come on
My Allah..
You couldn't get used to it yet?
Your heart hurts whenever
Alaaddin goes on a mission.
I couldn't, mother.
How did you get used to it?
Your husband and sons are always fighting.
Tell me. How do you endure this, mother?
Their fight is in the battlefield
and ours is here, girl.
Our fight is to keep our people
safe and cover our fears with faith.
My heart always hurts.
Not only for Osman and my children...
...but also for the raided village, the
world of Islam and all the innocent people.
You will get used to it.
Allah is Eternal!
Allah is The Righteous!
Allah is the greatest!
For my father!
Damn it.
Hristo!
My Bey, he's running off!
Osman
You won today, but tomorrow...
...I will take your heart
out and make wolves eat it!
Don't run away if you have courage, dastard!
Tie this rope somewhere solid, Hristo.
Will we leave Akhisar to Turks, commander Lukas?
The army of Nikea will never arrive, Hristo.
If we want to stop Osman's
advance, we have to live.
Tie the rope immediately.
He's out of range, my Bey.
He can't run away anymore.
He's going to die soon.
The castle of Akhisar belongs to Kayis now!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Alps, don't you hear?
Raise the glorious banners of Kayi!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Attention! Osman Bey!
This raid we started thinking that we
have campaigns and Allah offers victory...
...is crowned with a conquest.
Now this place will be enlightened
with the true religion Islam...
...and Akhisar will be reshaped
with the laws of Turks, God willing
This is the land of Turks now!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
My Bey, may your conquest be holy.
I've brought lots of regards
from the lands of Turks.
Peace be upon you too.
Thank you for that.
Samil.
You'll continue your duty.
You'll have the control of the frontiers.
Of course, my Bey.
May your conquest be holy, my Bey.
What's the matter, Alaaddin?
Is there a problem in the tribe?
My Bey.
The vile dog called Toyga
What about him?
He raided the tribes in the frontiers.
He burned down everything, my Bey.
Is that so?
I sent alps after him and warned everyone.
He was last seen in Demirbilek.
He is intimidating us, my Bey.
Trying to make us kneel.
If he has harmed people,
If even a single man has got hurt
...I will make their life miserable.
Get on horses! We will go make them pay
Osman
Damn it.
Damn it! Osman
I swear...
...I won't let you live
even at the cost of my life!
We'll make Osman face the most painful death.
Lukas.
I created such a trouble for Osman...
...that Mongolians won't let him take a break!
While Osman deal with Mongolians,
We will prepare his hell.
Everything he took from
us is going to destroy him.
Even a weapon.
Akhisar is just one of them.
And Osman won't realize anything
as he will have to deal with Mongolians.
Our victory is soon, Lukas.
We will take revenge.
You know Mongolians don't fight fairly, Sisters.
We should be prepared for any kind of fight.
Faster, stronger.
Meryem.
The threat of Mongolians is at the gate.
You need to learn how to protect
yourself as soon as possible.
You care about me so much
Fatma Hatun. Thank you.
You know what?
I also thought about this yesterday.
The moment I first saw you
..I felt close to you.
Maybe, you felt pity.
No. Not like that.
This is a feeling that I had
forgotten for a long time.
Whatever. Let's continue.
Come on, Meryem
Show your move.
That's it.
Come on, Meryem. Make your move.
No, no.
Check if there are any wounded men!
Mother, wake up... Mother...
How could you kill my innocent people?
How could you do this?
What did these people do to you?
Mother wake up. Mother..
Come, my dear. Come.
Come. Come.
Come.. My dear.
They killed my mother, Osman
Bey. They burned our tribe down.
Why did they do this?
You will make them pay
for this, right, Osman Bey?
Don't worry.
Would I ever let them get away with this?
Would I? My dear...
Don't be afraid..
Even if a thousand of them come...
...I will not let any of
them live on these lands.
I swear.
Osman
I was looking for you
Boran.
You infidel...
I'm coming from the tribe down there.
You should go there as well.
You should see the strength of Mongols.
I will now...
You killed my people.
You killed my innocent people.
You killed my children.
Are you going to bring me to account?
Who are you to stand against the Mongol state
You cannot do anything to me.
I came here...
...as the envoy of the Mongol state.
And you gave your answer.
From now on...
...you are not facing...
...the envoy of the Mongol
state, but its Commander!
These heads..
...are the response to your answer.
If you do not kneel and
pledge allegiance, your sons...
...your Hatun, your daughter
will die the same way.
Kneel and pledge allegiance Osman!
Even if the whole world
collapses on me, I will only give...
...blood and bones to you
You are making a mistake Osman.
Who are you? Who?
Come here!
Stand up! Stand up!
Your people will die, Osman
Your lands will turn into a bloodbath.
The dead in their graves... they will
dig up all their bones and burn them.
I swear...
I and the ones behind me...
...until the sun..
...rises from the west...
...will always exist...
...for dogs like you
Dastard dog
You will see Osman...
You will see the strength of Mongols...
You will see the strength of Commander Ulugan.
But you won't be able to see it.
We always have valiants on these lands.
But those like you...
But those like you won't be
able to take a step on these lands.
Make him bow!
You cannot..
...stand against...
...Mongols, Osman.
I am not only standing against them...
I am also cutting their heads off!
We have fought with many enemies.
Thanks to my Allah, we always
gained a victory and defeated them.
But you should know.
Mongols have always been troublesome.
Thus, send word to everyone.
To all tribes, to all castles!
Now everyone should know, the
war of existence for Turks has begun
We will either be martyrs,
or we will exist forever!
Allah is the Greatest!
Holy Commander Ulugan.
I gained Kayis' trust.
I became the most trustworthy Alp of Osman.
Osman cut Toygar's head off.
I am waiting for your order to make a move.
I am Osman Bey, of the
Oghuz Turks, from the Kayi tribe.
In these frontiers, where the few
have gained a victory over the many...
...I have never bowed to oppression.
Many became one against me...
...and they attacked me at once.
I fought without having a rest or giving up.
I am speaking to those who are worried
that jackals will get in the wolf's den.
Victory is ours, oppression is theirs.
Honor and shahada are for us.
Suffering and death are for them.